===PDF_TEXT_START===
Contact
nickpetty@hotmail.com
www.linkedin.com/in/nicholasepetty
(LinkedIn)
Top Skills
Interviewing
Test Automation
TestRail
Languages
English  (Native or Bilingual)
French  (Elementary)
Japanese  (Limited Working)Nicholas Petty
Senior QA Engineer at Modernizing Medicine
Boynton Beach, Florida, United States
Summary
I'm hard-working and dedicated, I learn quickly and develop my skills
to their fullest.  I enjoy teaching and working with technology and
hope to continue growing my career in these fields.
Experience
Modernizing Medicine
Senior Quality Assurance Engineer
January 2018á-áPresentá (8 years 2 months)
Boca Raton, Florida
Quality Assurance Engineer at Modernizing Medicine, working on the Practice
Management system in the Electronic Medical Assistant product.
ò Manual Testing of user stories in Jira.
ò Test cases managed in TestRail.
ò UI and API test automation code written in Java with Selenium.
ò Code repository managed in Git.
ò Interviewed and trained new QA Engineers and SDETs.
DSS, Inc.
9 months
QA Analyst III
October 2017á-áJanuary 2018á (4 months)
North Palm Beach, Florida
Quality Assurance Analyst on DSS's Fee Basis Claims System web
application, a workflow automation tool for many of the clerical tasks involved
in receiving claims from service providers outside of the VA.
ò Write and execute manual test cases for user stories and bugs.
ò Write, execute, and manage automated web GUI tests.
ò Web application is written in C# and AngularJS, with SQL database.
ò Automated tests are written in C# with NUnit and Selenium frameworks.
ò Project management with Jira, Confluence, and Rally.
ò Helped lead and train during adoption of Atlassian products.
QA Analyst II
á Page 1 of 3

á á
May 2017á-áOctober 2017á (6 months)
North Palm Beach, Florida Area
Quality assurance analyst on the Fee Basis Claims System (FBCS) web
application project.  Specifically focused on development of an automated
testing system using C# and Selenium.
Unify
Student Co-op in Quality Assurance and Software Engineering
June 2014á-áMay 2017á (3 years)
Boca Raton, Florida
Quality Assurance engineer for Circuit - a team collaboration and
communication tool built on WebRTC.
ò Managed the manual and automated testing systems for the telephony
connector feature
ò Used internal tools written in Java and Groovy for automated testing
ò Reported issues in Jira and documented projects in Confluence
ò Fixed bugs in Angular, Node.js, and Java
ò Deployed and maintained servers and network infrastructure with SUSE
Linux and vSphere
ò Performed manual regression and sanity tests for the iOS app
ò Fixed bugs on iOS in Objective-C and Swift in Xcode
Software engineer on the OpenScape Voice Trace Manager project - a tool for
collecting and analyzing messages in a SIP phone network.
ò Performed manual regression and sanity tests, and managed the test
database in HP ALM
ò Used ClearQuest to report, respond to, and resolve bugs in the application
ò Implemented features and fixed bugs with Visual Studio in VB.NET and
SQLite
Apple
Family Room Specialist
November 2012á-áJune 2014á (1 year 8 months)
Boca Raton, Florida
ò Troubleshot and repaired iOS devices and Macs at the Genius Bar
ò Taught workshops on Apple hardware and software
ò Worked with customer support teams to develop and implement repair
procedures and systems
Berlitz Japan
Instructor
March 2009á-áSeptember 2012á (3 years 7 months)
á Page 2 of 3

á á
Taught English as a second language to children and adults. Classes were
delivered to small and large businesses and universities.  Worked on test
preparation and curriculum development
Education
Florida Atlantic University
Master's degree,áComputer Science á╖á(2016á-á2017)
Florida Atlantic University
Bachelor of Science (B.S.),áComputer Science á╖á(2014á-á2015)
University of Florida
Bachelor of Science (BS),áMathematics á╖á(1999á-á2003)
á Page 3 of 3
===PDF_TEXT_END===
